Guide to the Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society Records, 1961-2009 AIS.1998.51
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Concert Programs, 1974-2016; VII.
  - Programs, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Programs, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Programs, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Programs, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Programs, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Programs, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Programs, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Programs, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Programs, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Programs, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Programs, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Programs, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Programs, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Programs, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Programs, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Programs, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Programs, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Programs, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Programs, 2010-2011 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Programs, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Programs, 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 2015-2016 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Financial Materials, 1982-2014; VIII.
  - Financial, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Financial, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Financial, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Financial, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Financial, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Financial, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Financial, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Financial, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Financial, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Financial, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Financial, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Financial, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Financial, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Financial, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Financial, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Financial, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Financial, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Financial, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Financial, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Financial, 2008-2009 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Financial, 2010-2011 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Financial, 2011-2012 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Financial, 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Financial, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Planning Documents, 1984-2014; IX.
  - Planning, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Planning, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Planning, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Planning, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Planning, 2008-2009 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Planning, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Planning, 2010-2011 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Planning, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Promotional Materials, 1976-2019; X.
  - Promotional, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Promotional, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Promotional, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Promotional, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Promotional, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Promotional, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Promotional, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Promotional, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Promotional, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Promotional, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Promotional, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Promotional, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Promotional, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Promotional, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Promotional, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Promotional, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Promotional, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Promotional, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Promotional, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Promotional, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Promotional, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Promotional, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Promotional, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Promotional, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Promotional, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Promotional, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Promotional, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Promotional, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Promotional, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Promotional, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Promotional, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Promotional, 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Promotional, 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Promotional, 2009-2010 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Promotional, 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Promotional, 2011-2012 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Promotional, 2012-2013 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Promotional, 2013-2014 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Promotional, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Promotional, 2015-2016 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Promotional, 2016-2017 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Promotional, 2017-2018 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Promotional, 2018-2019 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Review, 2000-2014; XI.
  - Reviews, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Reviews, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Reviews, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Reviews, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Reviews, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Reviews, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Reviews, 2006-2007 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Reviews, 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Reviews, 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Reviews, 2009-2010 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Reviews, 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Reviews, 2011-2012 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Reviews, 2012-2013 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Topical Folders, 1961-2014; XII.
  - Artists on CMP Concerts, 1961-2019 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Braille Document, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Bridges 2, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Concert Programs (other groups), 1992-2014 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Correspondences, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Correspondences, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Correspondences, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Correspondences, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Montgomery Fellowship, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Montgomery Fellowship, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Perfomance/Performers Index Cards, 1961-2003 (Box 11)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Proclamations, 2000-2008 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Percussion Effect, 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Teachers Guide, Bartok's Red Apple, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Teachers Guide, Bartok Night, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Works Performed at CMP, 1961-2019 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Audio-Visual Materials (Electronic Materials), 2008-2013; XIII.
  - Concert Records on Compact Discs, 2008-2013; 1.
  - DVD's, 2009-2012; 2.